<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- 
// 
// This is the place for your statements. The maximum 
// number of statements is theoretically unlimited, but
// less then 50 statements are advisable.
// If your are using German Umlauts and other special 
// characters, make sure, that you save this XML-file 
// as an UTF-8-document. White-space inbetween the 
// nodes are ignored. Any white-space within the text-
// nodes, including leading or trailing whitespace and 
// line breaks, is preserved.
//
// EXAMPLE
// Let's define some statements concerning FlashQ:
// Statement 1: FlashQ is very usefull.
// Statement 2: I prefer offline surveys.
// Statement 3: FlashQ is too complicated to configure.
//
// Each statement requires a seperate statement-node 
// consisting out of an opening and a closing tag. The 
// statement itself goes between this two tags. 
// The unique statement id is saved as an 
// attribute called 'id'. We have three exmaple 
// statements and we need therefore three statement-
// nodes and one parent-node. 
//
// <statements version="1.0" htmlparse="false">
//   <statement id="1">FlashQ is very usefull.</statement>
//   <statement id="2">I prefer offline surveys.</statement>
//   <statement id="3">FlashQ is too complicated to configure</statement>
// </statements>
// 
// ===================================================
// 
-->

<statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
  <statement id="0">MC-p: Alerts and reminders for visits and appointments would be helpful for my family.</statement>
<statement id="1">MC-n: I am concerned about potential issues with AI-based recommendations for managing family tasks.</statement>
<statement id="2">MC-p: Shared to-do lists with priorities would be useful for managing tasks in my family.</statement>
<statement id="3">MC-n: I am concerned about potential issues with using a list of pre-defined tasks within my family to complete.</statement>
<statement id="4">I-p: Syncing medical data and calendar on the cloud across devices would be beneficial for my family.</statement>
<statement id="5">I-n: I am concerned about potential difficulties in communicating using text message channels.</statement>
<statement id="6">I-p: A collaborative tracker for tracking symptoms and medicines would be helpful for my family.</statement>
<statement id="7">I-n: I am concerned about potential issues with generating updates and summaries from the content of audio calls and messages.</statement>
<statement id="8">MA-p: A list of predefined accommodation options would be helpful for my family.</statement>
<statement id="9">MA-n: I am concerned about potential issues with using an AI Finance Management tool for tracking expenses.</statement>
<statement id="10">MA-p: AI Finance management tool recommendations would be useful for managing my family's finances.</statement>
<statement id="11">MA-n: I am concerned about potential difficulties with using AI-generated recommendations for finance management.</statement>
<statement id="12">ME-p: Shared family collaborative activities would be beneficial for my family.</statement>
<statement id="13">ME-n: I am concerned about potential challenges with setting milestones in the treatment process and celebrating virtually.</statement>
<statement id="14">ME-p: Reflecting on our mental health using a digital journal would be helpful for my family.</statement>
<statement id="15">ME-n: I am concerned about potential issues with achieving mindfulness through random positive affirmations throughout the day.</statement>
<statement id="16">E-p: Sharing happy memories with family members would be beneficial for my family.</statement>
<statement id="17">E-n: I am concerned about potential difficulties in coping with emotions and staying resilient through a psychologist's advice.</statement>
<statement id="18">E-p: FAQs and tips for navigating emotional struggles would be helpful for my family.</statement>
<statement id="19">E-n: I am concerned about potential issues with sharing negative feelings with a close friend or family member for advice or companionship.</statement>
</statements>